ngalih.com 2007-10-18

# Privacy Policy

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.ngalih.com/privacy-policy "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

## **NGALIH PRIVACY POLICY**

We know that you care about privacy. We shares your concern and want you to know what information we gather and how we use it.

This notice describes the Ngalih privacy policies and practices that we use in connection with our site. For this purpose, the “site” includes all the pages and features that are available to the public. By using the Ngalih, you agree to the practices and policies described in this privacy policy.

**Ngalih does not ask for Personal Identifiable Information**

Ngalih does not require that you provide personal identification information in order for you to use our search service. You do not have to register to use the Ngalih search service unless you want to participate in our revenue sharing program.

**Use of Anonymous Data**

We use anonymous data regarding our search users. For example, to responding to your search queries, we use your IP address, browser type, and anonymous information contained in cookies. (See discussion below about cookies.)  
Ngalih is supported by advertising revenue collected from advertising partners. The ads you get are always relevant to you because they are delivered based on your search terms.

We may monitor anonymous data to check for any abuse or misuse of our service.  
When you submit a query to us, we pass your query on to our search partner. We do not pass personally identifiable information about you (except such information as you might choose to include in your query). We do not have control over our search partners and are not responsible for their use of any information that is passed to them.

**Cookies**

Cookies are a commonly used technology on the Web, and they are used on Ngalih’s.  
Ngalih writes a cookie to your PC. A cookie is a small text file sent by our computer system that is stored on your PC for record-keeping purposes. The cookie remains on your hard drive until you remove it.

Ngalih does not link the information stored in cookies to any personal information. Nor do we include any information in the cookie on your PC. We do include in the cookie a unique number or identifier. The indentifier serves as a tracker that allows our system to know about repeated use on any basis. Ngalih also uses cookies to track each session on our site and to determine if you are logged in.  
Your browser has functionality that will allow you to prevent the use of cookies or to remove cookies. See your browser’s “Help” file for details. Note however that disabling cookies may adversely affect your ability to use Ngalih.

**Search**

Our search service automatically records (or “logs”) all queries and results of all search users. Our logs do not include any personally identifying information. As noted above, we do not require that you provide any personal information.  
We treat these logs as part of our anonymous data. Search log information may be used and analyzed for the same purposes as other anonymous data referred to above.

**Business Transfer or Sale  
**  
As Ngalih continues to develop its business, Ngalih may sell or buy businesses or assets of businesses or Ngalih may merge with another business. In such cases, stored data and information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Ngalih, a product or product line of Ngalih or if substantially all the assets of Ngalih are acquired, stored data and information may well be one of the transferred assets. If Ngalih decides to undergo such a transaction, Ngalih will post information regarding the change of possession on itss web site.

**Under the Age of 13**

In accordance with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (”COPPA”), Ngalih will not knowingly collect personally information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you should not use any function or service of our site that allows you to provide any personally identifiable information.

**Security**

We have a firewall and other security measures. However we do not warrant or guarantee any information security.
